myjackpot.com 2017-06-01

# Data privacy statement from MyJackpot.com

**Data Protection Declaration**

This data privacy policy informs you of which personal data is being collected by Whow Games as part of our Internet services and games. It also explains how that data is processed and used. The protection of your personal information is important to us.  
Your data is protected against unauthorized access and loss through the use of various electronic, technical, physical, administrative and contractual measures.  
Whow Games has taken the necessary technical and organizational precautions to ensure that the regulations for data privacy are respected both internally as well as by external service providers. 

**Table of Contents**

1\. Collection of data  
2\. Use of your data  
3\. Data transfer  
4\. Game Information and Partner Offers  
5\. Google Analytics  
6\. Online Behavioral Advertising  
7\. Social Media Plugins  
8\. Right of revocation, deletion of data  
9\. Information, viewing, and deletion of data

**1\. Collection of data**

Whow Games collects personal data provided by you upon registration at one of our websites or for one of our games; when these are provided by you during an inquiry; when these are provided by you for the use and payment of fee­based goods and services; at your request for the purpose of participating in promotions and surveys, or to receive newsletters.

Whow Games also collects user data to the extent that it is necessary for the performance of services or for the billing of these services. This refers in particular to game processes, game scores and information regarding the use and settlement of services. We obtain information relating to our German users' past payment behavior from infoscore Consumer Data GmbH, Rheinstr. 99, 76532 Baden­Baden. Provided that you have used the Portal or Games and Services for an extended period of time, we would like to inform you that we also use data from our predecessor Company, and current subsidiary, Whow Games GmbH, Trostbrücke 1, 20457 Hamburg, Germany. This refers to master data that we require to continue offering games without interruption. This data especially refers to game processes, game scores and information regarding the use and settlement of services. Within the context of the use of our websites, forums and games, Whow Games collects the following non­personal information:

IP addresses including time and date cookies, local flash data statistical information such as the browser type, operating system, redirecting URL, date, time, pages used, total time of use, frequency of use. This data is used in statistical analyses for anonymous data records.  
IP addresses and the corresponding Internet information are saved for a period of maximum of six months within the scope of our legal obligations regarding data storage. Furthermore, these are stored to secure data and ensure our system’s stability and reliability. In specific situations, Whow Games may also use your IP address and the corresponding Internet information to track and stop use of multiple accounts for fraudulent purposes. In cases such as these, Whow Games will seek the consent for such use within the framework of the relevant game conditions.

Cookies Authorization:  
Despite the fact that this is stated in the Data Privacy Policy, we would like to expressly inform you that we employ the use of cookies to optimize the use of our Portal and Games and Services, especially regarding user experience. By accepting our Terms and Conditions, you authorize the use of cookies. At any point in the future, you can object to the use of cookies by sending an e­mail to the following address info@whow.net. For all additional questions regarding cookies, please contact us via the same email address.

Our online service uses the "Scalable Central Measuring method" (SCM / SCMnG) from INFOline Ltd. GmbH (https ://www.infonline.de ) to determine statistical values for the use our offers. Anonymous measured data will be collected. For the recognition of computer systems, the SCM measurement method alternatively uses either a cookie with the ID “ioam.de”, "ivwbox.de", a local storage object or a signature that is automatically created from different browser­transmitted information. IP addresses are only processed in anonymous form. The range measurement was developed under strict observation of data protection policies. The objective of the range measurement system is to statistically determine how intensely and by how many users a website is being used. At no point in time will individual users be identified. Their identities will always remain protected. They will receive no promotional materials via the system. For online offers that belong to the Association of the Distribution of Advertising Materials (Informationsgemeinschaft zur Feststellung der Verbreitung von Werbeträgern e.V., IVW – www.ivw.eu ) or are a part of the German Study Group for Online Research (Arbeitsgemeinschaft Online­Forschung e.V., AGOF – www.agof.de ) study, "Internet Facts," the usage statistics will be published on a monthly basis by AGOF, the Working Group of Media Analysis (Arbeitsgemeinschaft Media­Analyse e.V., ag.ma ­ www.agma­mmc.de ), as well as by the IVW. The results can be viewed at: http://www.agof.de , http://www.agma­mmc.de and http://www.ivw.eu . In addition to the publication of measured data, the IVW regularly checks the SCM process to make sure it stays consistent with the rules of data protection. Additional information about the SCM process can be found on the INFOnline GmbH website (https ://www.infonline.de ), which operates the system itself, on the AGOF's data protection website (http://www.agof.de/datenschut z), as well as on the IVW's data protection website (http://www.ivw.eu ). You can object to SCM processing your data via the following website: http://optout.ioam.de and http://optout.ivwbox.de.

 **2\. Use of your data**

We use your personal data to provide our services and settle payments; to anonymously or pseudonymously adjust our offer to meet our users’ demands and improve our services; to fulfill legal obligations, and in particular, to meet the requirements for preserving data. We also use this information to communicate with you. This includes, in particular, the provision of assistance and support as well as the provision of important contract information. Subject to your consent, we keep you informed about news, events and promotions either via e­mail, phone call or text message.

 **3\. Data transfer**

We treat your data with strict confidentiality. Your confidential data shall not be disclosed to any third parties unless you have given us your express written permission to do so or we are contractually obligated to transfer this data. In certain situations (such as if requested by an investigating authority), we may however be required by law to disclose your information. In such cases, the transfer shall only take place within the framework required by legal conventions. In individual cases, subsidiaries, parent companies or Third Parties may provide services on our behalf. This mainly concerns the handling of payment transactions by external service providers (PayPal, Global Collect, etc.) and, in the case of default, by a debt collection company. Moreover, we provide your data ­ for marketing purposes ­ to external companies that are engaged in a contractual relationship with Whow Games so as to further develop and improve our games. Should we be contractually obligated to transfer your data to a Third Party, the respective Third Party shall be enabled and permitted to use this data in order to communicate with you. As such, the external companies and Third Parties are also obligated to handle your data securely and in a confidential manner.

 **4\. Game Information and Partner Offers**

By checking the box next to "Game Information and Partner Offers", you are granting us your express consent to receive this information. Your consent will be recorded and saved, and may be revoked at any time by using our contact form (support@whow.net).

 **5\. Google Analytics**

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyse how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. If, however, you activate the Anonymize IP option on this website, Google will remove the end of your IP address so it only locates you as within the member states of the European Union or other members of the European Economic Area. Only in rare cases will the complete IP address be transmitted to a Google server in the USA and then shortened there.

Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and Internet usage. The operator of this website will use information gathered via interest­related advertising as well as third­party visitor data (e.g. age, gender and interests) for the purpose of evaluation in order to find out more about the users of this website. No person­related data shall be used here; only a statistical evaluation of anonymous data sets shall be carried out. Google will not associate your IP address as transmitted by Google Analytics with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. Furthermore, you can prohibit Google from collecting and analysing the data generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) by downloading and installing the browser plugin available here http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout. Should you wish to adapt or prevent the analysis of your demographic or interest­based information, you can disable Google Analytics display ads and adapt the ads in the Google Display Network: https ://www.google.com/settings/ads .

 **6\. Online Behavioral Advertising**

The advertising on our websites will be optimized according to your predicted interests by collecting and processing anonymous data about your usage of our websites. German telecommunications provider ProSiebenSat.1 Digital GmbH, in cooperation with online marketing company SevenOne Media GmbH, a subsidiary of the ProSiebenSat.1 Group and ProSiebenSat.1 Digital GmbH, in accordance with §§ 15 ff of the German Stock Corporation Act, is responsible for collecting the aforementioned data. To this end, third party companies place cookies on your computer to collect user data. The data collected is information when, for example, you navigate the pages of this online offer or click on ads. This allows us to analyze the use of online ads and to provide you with ads that could be of interest to you and correspond to your personal preferences (Online Behavioral Advertising). No personal information, such as name, address, e­mail address etc., will be collected. IP addresses are kept anonymous so that they cannot be allocated to any specific person.

If you want to opt out of receiving Online Behavioral Advertising, you can block the placement of cookies on your computer by changing your browser settings so that it does not accept cookies. Furthermore, you may prevent third­party companies, employees on our behalf, from using cookies via the following links:  
Nugg.ad AG: http://ad­choices.nuggad.net  
AudienceScience: http://www.audiencescience.com/de/privacy  
Criteo GmbH: http://www.criteo.com/us/privacy­policy

Additionally, we permit other third parties, e.g. media agencies, to use cookies to analyze the use of online advertising and to display advertising in our online offer that could be of interest to you by analyzing your personal preferences. Additionally, this should enable advertising customers to reach their target audience more accurately without large wastage. For this purpose, user statistics can, for example, be anonymously compiled and the data can be used for market research purposes, without tracing this information back to a specific person. Further information about this provider's Data Privacy Policy and about objecting to the use of cookies for the purpose of usage­based online advertising can be found on SevenOne Media GmbH's website at:  
https ://www.sevenonemedia.de/web/sevenone/datenerhebung­anderer­dienstleister 1. You can also control the placement of third­party cookies on your computer through a respective setting on your browser.

SevenOne Media GmbH has voluntarily agreed to comply with the self­regulatory principles of the German Privacy Policy Council for Online Advertising (DDOW ­ Deutschen Datenschutzrat Online­ Werbung). The self­regulatory code valid for us (Code for Telemedia Providers ­ First Parties) can be found at: www.meine­cookies.org/ddow.html.

 **7\. Social Media Plugins**

Facebook

Embedded on our website are various Facebook links. This web presence is operated exclusively by Facebook Inc., 1601 S California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA (Facebook). Within the scope of our web presence, these links are identified by the Facebook logo or by the phrase 'Like' (no Facebook plugins are used).

Should a user click one of these links, then the Facebook plugins are activated and establish a direct connection via the user's browser to a Facebook server.

Provided that the user clicks one of the aforementioned links while visiting our website, and is logged into their personal Facebook account, the information will be forwarded to Facebook that the user has visited our website. Facebook can associate your visit to the website to your account. This data is transferred to and saved by Facebook. To prevent this, the user must log out of their account before clicking the link. The functions embedded in the links by Facebook, especially the transfer of data and user information, are not activated by visiting our website, but rather by clicking the corresponding links.

The purpose and scope of data collection via Facebook, the processing and use of such data, as well as your rights thereof and personal settings regarding privacy protection can be found in the Facebook privacy settings section (http://de­de.facebook.com/privacy/explanation.php ).

For further questions pertaining to the collection, processing or use of individual user data, as well as regarding disclosing, correcting, blocking or deleting data, please contact our data protection supervisors.

Google Plus

Our web presence also employs the Google Plus "+1" link, which is operated by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, United States (Google). The link can be identified by the "+1" symbol against a white or color background.

If the user opens one of our websites containing such a link, the user's browser establishes a direct connection to a Google server. The contents of the "+1" link are transferred directly to your browser, which then integrates said content in the webpage. We therefore have no control over the data whatsoever that Google collects via the link, but would expect user IP addresses to be collected.

The purpose and scope of data collection via Google, the processing and use of such data, as well as your rights thereof and personal settings regarding privacy protection can be found in the Google privacy settings section http://www.google.com/intl/de/+/policy/+1button.html If a user is a Google Plus member and does not wish to have their data collected and linked to their saved Google member data via our web presence, the the user must log out of their Google Plus account before visiting our websites.

 **8\. Right of revocation, deletion of data**

If you have given us consent to process personal data, you can withdraw this consent at any time. Whow Games deletes your personal data insofar as it is no longer needed or required, or if you have requested the deletion of this data. Please note that data cannot be deleted if there are legal storage requirements or this data is required by us for the billing of our services.

 **9\. Information, viewing, and deletion of data**

At info@whow.net you can request to see data which we have recorded, as well as request to have this data changed or deleted. You may also send your request by standard mail to the following address: 

Whow Games GmbH Trostbrücke 1  
20457 Hamburg  
Germany
